<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TipsOfTheDay>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can download tags for music from an online databasis? Just select "Edit Tags" from the context menu
	of a folder or file in the Music Explorer and then click on Download on the right side.
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... to play a single sound on the press of a key or button, it's best to use a sequential list with just a 
	single element?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... there are now some <a href="http://sourceforge.net/p/aresrpg/discussion/English/">discussion forums</a>
	to Ares online?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can upload tags into the online databasis after you have selected them for music files? Then, other
	users can download them in turn. To upload, use the "Share" button in the Tags window.
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can set effects and volume for files by making a double-click on the file in the list or by 
	selecting the effect from the context menu of the file in the list?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can get an overview of the used keys in the project through the menu View - Used Keys?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can export modes or elements from the context menu of the Project Explorer and then import them
	into other projects?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can select an editor for audio files (e.g. Audacity) in the settings (tools)? Then you can edit
	the files from the File or Music Explorer.
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can filter in the Music Explorer using tags with the right-most button in the toolbar of the
	Music Explorer?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can export the whole project with all audio files in packed form through the Project menu? Then
	you can easily take it with you to the game. You can also take the Ares Player / Controller with you, there's
	a portable version to download.
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can reorder elements and modes in the Project Explorer with the buttons to the right in the toolbar?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... the Ares Player has an option to play music on all speakers?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can undo all changes on a project through the Edit menu or the toolbar?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... the Ares Controller is also available as an Android app?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can 'script' komplex music and sound situations easily with macros? You insert a macro in the 
	context menu of a mode in the Project Explorer.
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can select an external music player in the settings (tools)? It will then be used to "pre-listen" 
	to music in the Music Explorer.
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... lists in the project can be nested? E.g. you can put several sequential lists into a parallel list and
	thus let them run in parallel.
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... you can search for files in the Music and Sound Explorers through their toolbar?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... Ares Player and Controller have an option to react on key presses even if another program is active?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... elements can be reused in several modes or lists? To do that, copy the element into the clipboard and
	then select "Paste as Link" from the context menu of the target.
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... the online database at <a href="http://rpgmusictags.org">rpgmusictags.org</a> already contains tags for
	more than 1300 music files ready for download?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... there are online <a href="http://aresrpg.sourceforge.net/en/hilfe/Start.html">help pages</a> with descriptions
	of Ares?
  </p></Tip>
  <Tip><p>
    ... Ares is open source published under the GPL?
  </p></Tip>
</TipsOfTheDay>